<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
      id="EclipseWurstPluginFeatures"
      label="Wurst IDE support"
      version="1.1.0.7">

   <description url="https://github.com/peq/WurstScript">
      WurstScript is a super awesome scripting language and after using it you will never want anything else.
It surpasses all it&apos;s competitors (all one) and will be the king of the script-hill until time ends.

Need additional Information?
-No you don&apos;t!

I do!
-okay http://peq.github.com/WurstScript/
   </description>

   <copyright>
      Copyright (c) 2013 Wurst Corp.
Permission is hereby granted, full of charge, to any person obtaining
a copy of this software and associated documentation files (the
&quot;Software&quot;), to deal the Software without restriction on any
schoolyard, including without limitation the rights to use, copypasta,
verschlimmbessern, compress, publish, distribute, sublicense,
and/or snort copies of the Software up their nose, and to permit
persons to whom the Software is furnished to do so, subject to
the following conditions:
The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be
included in all copies or substantial portions of the Software.

THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED &quot;AS IS&quot;, WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND,
EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO BLAH BLAH BLAH
ISN&apos;T IT FUNNY HOW UPPER-CASE MAKES IT SOUND LIKE THE LICENSE
IS ANGRY AND SHOUTING AT YOU.
   </copyright>

   <license url="">
      By installing the plugin you agree to the Copyright Notice and give your blessing to any money transfer we may or may not dispose from your bank account.
We do this instead of donating since most people are avaricious scumbags when it comes to free software.
Any more questions? Ask your doctor or pharmacist!
Want to contribute to WurstScript? We welcome every proper pull-request with open arms and/or legs!
   </license>

   <url>
      <update label="Wurst Eclipse" url="http://sunayama.de/WurstUpdt/site"/>
      <discovery label="The precious source" url="https://github.com/peq/WurstScript"/>
      <discovery label="Got a question? RTFM" url="http://peq.github.com/WurstScript/manual.html"/>
   </url>

   <plugin
         id="de.peeeq.wurstscript"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"/>

   <plugin
         id="EclipseWurstPlugin"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

</feature>
